- ConversationTopicId: 01_Grace_Goodbye_WW
  PlayerPrompt: "@01_Grace_Goodbye_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@01_Grace_Goodbye_a_new"
  AchievementUnlock: 01_Grace_Goodbye_WW
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 01_Grace_Goodbye_MB
  PlayerPrompt: "@01_Grace_Goodbye_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@01_Grace_Goodbye_a_new"
  AchievementUnlock: 01_Grace_Goodbye_MB
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 01_Grace_Goodbye_WW_Final
  PlayerPrompt: "@01_Grace_Goodbye_next2_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@01_Grace_Greet_04_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: 01_Grace_Goodbye_WW
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 01_Grace_Goodbye_MB_Final
  PlayerPrompt: "@01_Grace_Goodbye_next2_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@01_Grace_Greet_04_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: 01_Grace_Goodbye_MB
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 01_boarfeast_topicTime
  PlayerPrompt: "@01_boarfeast_topicTime_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@01_boarfeast_topicTime_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 01_boarfeast_topicTime_MB
  PlayerPrompt: "@01_boarfeast_topicTime_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@01_boarfeast_topicTime_a_MB"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 01_boarfeast_topicOrigin
  PlayerPrompt: "@01_boarfeast_topicOrigin_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@01_boarfeast_topicOrigin_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 01_boarfeast_topicOrigin_MB
  PlayerPrompt: "@01_boarfeast_topicOrigin_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@01_boarfeast_topicOrigin_a_MB"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 01_crewmates_topicCorrupted
  PlayerPrompt: "@01_crewmates_topicCorrupted_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@01_crewmates_topicCorrupted_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 01_crewmates_topicCorrupted_MB
  PlayerPrompt: "@01_crewmates_topicCorrupted_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@01_crewmates_topicCorrupted_a_MB"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
